Guide to the Irene Peslikis Papers, 1957-2002 and undated RL.01018
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1969-1971, 1978-1980, 1991, and undated, 3 boxes
  - Audiocassettes, 1970-1991; 1
    - First class on Hegel, 9
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0009)
    - Irene Peslikis, 1991 Apr. 25, 10
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0010)
    - Joana and Irene fighting and reciting, 11
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0011)
    - Greek, 12
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0012)
    - Leslie, Irene, and Susan, 1970, 13
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0013)
    - Lousy tape of men and Ray Shitzler, radio interview, 14
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0014)
    - Lucia and Irene and approach avoidance, 1979 Nov. 9, 15
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0015)
    - My tape, 16
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0016)
    - Pat and Helen, 17
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0017)
    - Que..., 18
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0018)
    - Women's Lib: Redstockings: single women and married women question, why we got married, why we do want to get married, 19
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0019)
    - Women's Lib: Redstockings: single women and married women question, why we got married, why we do want to get married, 20
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0020)
    - Redstockings: If we are married, how do we feel about single women; if we are single, how do we feel about married women?, 21
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0021)
    - Redstockings: If we are married, how do we feel about single women; if we are single, how do we feel about married women?, 22
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0022)
    - Redstockings: If we are married, how do we feel about single women; if we are single, how do we feel about married women?, 23
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0023)
    - Redstockings: If we are married, how do we feel about single women; if we are single, how do we feel about married women?, 24
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0024)
    - Are men oppressed as men? Redstockings, 1969 Sept. 3, 25
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0025)
    - Are men oppressed as men? Redstockings, 1969 Sept. 3, 26
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0026)
    - R and I, 27
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0027)
    - R and I, 28
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0028)
    - R and I, aftermath and fight, 29
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0029)
    - Toes/free, 30
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0030)
    - untitled, 31
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0031)
    - untitled, 32
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0032)
    - untitled, 33
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0033)
    - V. F. Women, approach/avoidance, 34
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0034)
    - Women and Art opening, 35
      - Original audiocassette (Box 41, Audio-cassette RL01018-CS-0035)
    - OR-36 Walter and Irene, 1971 Oct. 29 (Box 41)
      [Note: Item removed to Box 43.]Enter scope/content note.
    - OR-37 WNYC radio interview on program, New York Now, M regarding her art exhibit at Noho Galleries (Box 41)
  - Film and Video
    - Beach, car window (Box 42)
    - Beach, Helen and Roy (Box 42)
    - Beverly and Robin (Box 42)
    - Boat ride, NRDC (Box 42)
    - Boat ride and trailer (Box 42)
    - Box (Box 42)
    - Chair and ditch (Box 42)
    - Community meeting and Westbeth festival (Box 42)
    - Community meeting #2, Feldman's feet (Box 42)
    - Crested bottle (Box 42)
    - Crested bottle #2 (Box 42)
    - Dawn on school roof (Box 42)
    - Film developed 1980 Oct. 10, 2 Reels 2 super 8 film reels (Box 42)
    - Helen and Roy's opening (Box 42)
    - Kay Brown and slide (Box 42)
    - Laundry (Box 42)
    - Marilyn and some television (Box 42)
    - My Water Hock Stuff #1200 (Box 42)
    - Namis stuff (Box 42)
    - Peslikis's work from Feminist Art Institute (Box 42)
    - Ribbing (Box 42)
    - Ribbed glass and table at Ear Inn (Box 42)
    - Still life (Box 42)
    - Sue Knoll at Feminist Art Institute (Box 42)
    - Sunset and moon at Westbury (Box 42)
    - Susquehana, 4 Reels 4 super 8 film reels (Box 42)
    - Trailer (Box 42)
    - Train and tree on Saint Marks Place (Box 42)
    - Television, Beth Lord, and community meeting #1 (Box 42)
    - Two punk people at Ear Inn (Box 42)
    - Westbeth festival, opera gallery, and Westbury from a cab (Box 42)
    - Westbury feminist and art show, 2 Reels 2 super 8 film reels (Box 42)
    - Irene Peslikis memorial (Box 43)
    - Sunset (Box 43)
    - Untitled (Box 43)
- Miscellaneous Oversize
  - Miscellaneous (Oversize-folder 1, Oversize-folder 2, Oversize-folder 3)